Wrege, Charles D. Research Papers 6395
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Charles D. Wrege Research Papers
1925-2013
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wrege, Charles D.
6395
12.5 cubic feet
12.5 linear ft.
Articles, reports, pamphlets, correspondence, photographs, papers.
8686986
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 07, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 11, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Charles "Chuck" Wrege finished his undergraduate degree in Upsala College, obtained his Masters degree at the New School fo Social Research and another Masters of Business Administration and his Ph.D. at NYU. He taught industrial management at Rutgers University for 30 years. He became a renowned historian, researcher and writer. He is regarded as a "National Treasure" by many in his field because of his expertise and the seminal research he has done in the area of management history.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arrangement
Series I: Western Electric and the Hawthorne Studies
Series II: Hstory of Incandescent Lighiting
Series III: Frederick W. Taylor
Series IV: Midvale Steel Company
Series V: Morris L. Cooke
Series VI: Frank B. Copley
Series VII: Pig Iron Loading Studies
Series VIII: Frank B. Gilbreth
Series IX: Fatigue Studies
Series X: Boxly: Frederick Taylor's Residence
Series XI: Rutgers University, the Academy of Management, and the History of Management
Series XII: Streetcars and Railroads
Series XIII: Personal
Series XIV: Hawthorne Productivity Charts
8686986
- Series I: Western Electric and the Hawthorne Studies
  - Two Drawings of Daniel Dr Drawbaugh's 1865 Telephone (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Early History of the Telephone - the electrician, May 1883, Vol. 2-5, pp. 129 & "Drawbaugh Defence" opinion of the court, Jan 23, 1884, 1883-1884 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Early Telephone of Dr. A. F. Pawley, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dugald C. Jackson and the Northern Electrical Mgf. Co. Taylor Hawthorne, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dynamogenic Factors in Hawthorne Illumination Tests, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Scope and Contents
    one sheet written in 1976
  - Edward B. Craft, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    May 23rd
  - G. Beowe Imphase Transmitter, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Santhorn Fire Map of the Hawthorne Works, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Western Electric Employer, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Organization of Western Electric Company, 1922-1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Western Electric & Bell Telephone charts etc., 1924 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - WE Balance Sheet, Vol. 15 #2 April 1926, p. 5, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Organizational Chart for Western Electric, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fred Willard, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Supervisory Training at Hawthorne, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AT&T 1930 Report (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - History of Western Electric, Frank Engli, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Supervisory Training Conference Series of Employee Performance, Conference No. 7, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    "Earlier Experiment on Employer Performances"
  - Western Electric Training Program, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dickson to Hibarger, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    June 20
  - MST Training Program WE, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Western Electric Bell System, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Material on Hawthorne - Compiled by C.D. R for Western Electric Training, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Richard H. Frazier Testroom Letters Hawthorne, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Western Electric History, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Panel Switching, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Western Electric Employee Information (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Photograph of Daniel Drawbaugh early telephone at Carlisle, PA (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Owen B. Hunt, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Hathaway Flow Chart Original (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Hawthorne's New Athletic Field, Western Electric News, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Diagram of Telephone Assembly Buildings at Hawthorne, 1924-1927 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Charts of WE Engineering April 1, 1915; Bell Labs, June 1, 1925; WE Engineering Department, March 25, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - K. W. Waterson; Problems of the Traffic Department, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Report on 1926 Tests Hawthorne (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Thermofax Copies of 1926, NRC Reports (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Dugold Jackson Memo to Pennock Feb. 25, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Conversion Factors in Piecerate Hawthorne, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Log of the Test Room, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Hawthorne Study Records from Microfiche, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Daily History Record, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Progress Reports, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Test to Determine the Effects of Rest Periods and Hours of Work (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Pennoch June 11, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Once a month performance check 6329
  - Daily History Notes, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Fred W. Willard correspondence on Hawthorne with Pennock, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Memorandum Respecting Conference to Introduce Illumination Tests at Hawthorne (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - An Investigation of Rest Pauses, Working Conditions, and Industrial Efficiency, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Richard Frazier letter to Mark Putnam on Hawthorne, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Speed Tests vs. Hours of Sleep at Hawthorne, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - An Introduction of Rest Pauses, Working Conditions, and Industrial Efficiency, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Data on Relays, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Fifteen Minute Speed Tests: Relay Group, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Relation Between Quality of Output & Hourly Output at Hawthorne (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - I. Rousseau - observation on test room increased production at Hawthorne, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Hawthorn Records, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - View of Hawthorne, Observers View of Test Room, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Development of More Scientific Points of View in the Hawthorne Experiments, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Photocopies of Research Report on Illumination and Production, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Hawthorn Studies in Robert Roy, The Admin Process, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Original List of Hawthorne Studies Documents Bob Lovette 1958 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Hibarger to Dickson, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    July 1
  - Hawthorne Experiment Bibliograph - Western Electric, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Thomas North Whitehead Data Industrial Worker, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Data on Edward Kimball Hall of Bell Telegraph (connects to Hawthorne Studies), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Pennock, Robert A., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Fagen on "Mechanical Switching" Step by Step, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - 901 Relay Data for Hawthorne -John Date, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Hawthorne Study Microfiche Index and Guide, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Richard Franice Data, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Ruth Wedelich data on 1924-1925 tests, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Marty Labno (photographer Hawthorne plant) correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    Chicago, Illinois
  - Data on Irving C. Whitemore and Hawthorne Illumination Tests, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Al Bolton on Gross Material - On Hawthorne, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Data on Relays (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Hawthorne Data (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Hawthorne Photographs (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Charles Snow Notebook Organic Chemistry (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Charles Snow Notebook Chemistry, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Mr. Snow's Diagram of Test Enclosure Illumination, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Management & Worker Book Log, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - C. Snow's Datasheets, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Chart H1 Snow, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - C. E. Snow Chart H-9 "Coil Winding Control Group", 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Piece Rates Data & Snow, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Snow's Logs, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Snow Log output, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Relay Assembly Efficiency noted by C. E. Snow, 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Snow Tests, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - C. E. Snow Chart #H110 "Test Group, #46, Induction Coils" (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Test Data from C. E. Snow, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Research on Industrial Illumination, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Snow Report (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Copies of Charles E. Snow's reports on Hawthorne Illumination Tests (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Selections from "An Observers Impression of the RATR", 1932 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Pemode to Hitrager, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    June 13
  - Bob McAllister, 7 Powderhouse RI, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    Dover, MA
  - Snow's Illumination Changes and Rate Increases, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Beginning of Test and Establishment of Testroom, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Test Room Layouts, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Output Tables (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Test Room Photographs, 1924-1927 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1925 Charts (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Snow Dec. 6 Tests, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1926 Tests (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1926 Chart of Output (Box 2, Folder 8)
    5 times a day and once per day
  - Test Room Attributes, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Relay Assembly Test Room Data, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Test Room Log Notes, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Relay Output at Base Period, Period 7&8, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Daily History Record, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Daily History - Test Room, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    May 27
  - Start of Search for Illumination Data, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Output Test Room, 1927-1932 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Noise & Bending 47-5 Map, 1927-1932 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Information on Workroom Company and the Workroom record output in the test room at Hawthorne, 1927-1933 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Test Room Output Progress Report 3, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Second Relay Assembly Group, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Relay Types in Test Room, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Daily History Record, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - W. E. on RATR, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Memo of 11/12/1930 from R. S. Meriam on Noise in Test Room at Hawthorne & 1964 letters to Meriam (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Schedule of Test Periods in Test Room, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Davisson, 1931 on Five Types of Relays for Test Room (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Weekly Activity Summary of Test Room, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - R8 Output Recorder Test Room, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Changes in the Program During 1931 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Western Electric Progress Report, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Weekly Activist Summary, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Richard D. Gross Chart of Test Room Output, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Test Room 12/19/31 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Relay Types Test Room, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Incentive Earnings in Test Room, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    March 19
  - Output Records in Test Room March 5, 1932 - February 11, 1933, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Whitehead's data on "Attention" and Output in Test Room, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Teletype - Perforator Data, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Test Room Output Charts (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - RATR Report (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Weekly Changes of Relay Types Experimented by Each Operator, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Guide to procedure used in relay assembly test room, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Hawthorne Output Data (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Test Room Output Graphic Transparencies (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Original Flowchart of Method to Calculate Weekly Savings in Relay Assembly Test Room, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hours Worked in Test Room, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    9 pages
  - Most Accurate Output Data of Test Room CDW, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Conversion Factors in Test Room, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Planning Test Room, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Dan Rotante on Test Room, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Data on the "Productivity Device" In the Test Room (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Test Room Periods 5-10 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Operator Data, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Operator Records, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Test Room Operator No. 2, 1927-1933 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Test Room Operator No. 3, 1927-1931 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - New Wage Rates in Test Room, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Test Room Operator No. 8, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - 1924-1925 Hit Incentive Earning (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Wage Rates of Operators in Test Room, 1925-1937 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - "Fire Output Checks Per Day", 1926 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    Summer
  - Original Piece Rate - Conversion Chart at Hawthorne, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Method of Payment, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Operator No. 3 Earnings, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Hawthorne, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Test Room Earnings periods 1-10, 1927-1930 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Wage Rates With Earning and Outputs, 1927-1932 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Actual Relays per Hour in TEST Room & Earnings, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Hourly & Weekly Earnings of 2nd Relay Group, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Calculation of Earnings in Test Room 9-4 to 9-8, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Earnings 3/1/32, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Daywork Rates in Test Room, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Percentage of earnings in Test Room Weeks 1-134, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Test Room Earnings: Weeks 8-62 (calculated in Original Forms), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Format for calculating earnings in test room at Hawthorne, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - 5/20/82 original rates in calculating earnings in test room, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Week Numbers and total hours worked in test room to calculate average hourly earning, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Earnings in Test Room Periods 1-13 and detailed analysis of period 11 & 12, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Computer printout of earnings in test room 8/9/85 weeks 1-269, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Earnings Calculations in Lamond, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - 2nd Retry Test Earnings, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - How To Determine Piece Rates in the Test Room, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Additional Income: Illumination Tests, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Analysis of Piece Parts; E-901, R-1316, R-1317 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Miscellaneous Lighting Data (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Weather in Chicago, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Comments on the "Transcript" of Professor Henry Lindenberger's Statements on "New Light on Hawthorne", 1964 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Physiological Orientation of Test Room, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Statistical Analysis of Output in Illumination Tests, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Analysis of Casey's 1978 paper on test room (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Differences in E-901, R-1316 and R-1317 Flat Type Relays, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - C. D. Wrege "How to Calculate Output Earnings in Test Room", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Calculating Output Forms, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Blank Forms for Calculating Weekly Earnings of Operators in 1927, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Chart of changes in Relay Types in Test Room (chart from Whitehead), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Hawthorne - test room calculations, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Dr. Richard Frazier Interview, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Hawthorne Effect first mentioned by R. P. French, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Computer printout of output in test room 1927-1932, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    marked "Figures ok, CDW, 9/4/83"
  - Issue Dr. Wreger Wages to Check On, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chart Showing How 6 Months Rate Revision Reduced Out put, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Five Checks Illuminated Tests 2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1925-1928 Output Analysis, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - R-1316, R-1317 Analysis, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 2nd Relay Assembly Test Group (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Actual Relay Output in Testroom by Converting Rely Output by E-901 to Actual (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and data for dissertation on Hawthorne, 1957-1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dr. Wrege's Hawthorne Correspondence, 1957-1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Dr. Wrege's Hawthorne Correspondence, 2006-2013 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Arthur Bedeian Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Steve Flocker Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with Philip S. Florence (England) on Hawthorne (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - G. Elton Mayo Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Greg Plungers Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dr. Wrege's C.E. Snow Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Reversal at Hawthorne, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hawthorne Hoax, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Solving Mayo's Mystery, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Before Mayo: Forgotten Experimenters and Experiments at Hawthorne, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Rest Periods in Test Room: 1925 Antecedents, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - In Defense of Hawthorne, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Discovering the Real Hawthorne, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - The Hawthorne Studies: An Iconoclastic Viewpoint, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Who Were Mayo's "Many Hands"?, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Charting the Hawthorne Studies: Day-by-Day Analysis, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Decisions at Hawthorne, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Greenwood and Wrege on the Hawthorne Studies, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Hawthorne Studies: Myth and Reality, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Dugald C. Jackson: The Forgotten First Direction of Hawthorne Studies, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Analysis of Women of Hawthorne, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Review of Hawthorne Studies, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bank Wiring Observation Form, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Hawthorne's "Silent Secrets", 2007 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Powerpoint for "Research for Hawthorne", 2007 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Preserving the Memory of Hawthorne, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Beneficial Effects of Ambient Noise, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - "Black Holes" of Hawthorne's, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Hawthorne's Films: Clues to Hawthorne's Secrets, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Output Recorder, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - The Question Still Is: What Caused the Hawthorne Effect?, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Test Room Notes, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Wage Incentive System at Hawthorne Draft, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Calculating the Average Hourly Earnings, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Comparison of Hawthorne Illumination Tests with Relay Assembly Test Room, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Hand Coil Winding, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Hawthorne Illumination Tests 1924-1925, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - McBerty, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Observations on Richard H. Franke and James D. Kanz, "The Hawthorne Experiments in First Statistics Interpretations", 2009 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Palimpsests and Hawthorne, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Proof That Money Plus Requisitions Explains Hawthorne, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Switchboards, "Peg Counts" and the Test Room, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Switchboard Price Trend, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Time to Assembly Relays, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Was there a "real" relay assembly test room, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - 1932 Incentive Earnings, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Authority Sheet AT&T 1925, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Conference With Relay Test Room Group Before Starting Study, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Creating New "Conversion Factors" In Test Room, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Earnings in the Relay Assembly Test Room, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Factors in Relay Assembly, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - "Management and Worker Didn't Tell Us or Told us Wrong", 2010 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Origins of Hawthorne Illumination Tests, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Output in Test Room and Fraud Schemes, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Panel Analysis, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Piece Rates 2010 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Relays and Foils 1920-1930, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Rest Period Committee, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Rest Periods in Test Room: 1925 Antecedents, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - 1924 Meeting to Plan Hawthorne Illuminating Tests, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - 1925 Western Electric Resolution in Manual Switchboard Prices, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Bonus Plans, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - "Cleveland-Main" Experiment, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - "Conversion Factor Questions", 2011 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - "Hawthorne Effect" Saga, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - "Increased Supervision" at Hawthorne, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Piece Rate Policy 1925, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Reaching "Auffassung" Regarding the Test Room, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Salting the Mine, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Snow's 1924-1925 Illumination Tests Earning Charts Analyzed, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Spotlight II on Output at Hawthorne, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Thick Insulators Problems: R-1316 Relay, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Truth: Real Output in Test Room, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1926 Bell Education Conference, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1929 Progress Report, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Story of Independent Telephony, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - A Tale of Two Pins, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - AT&T, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Actual Output Test Room Group Output by Periods (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Attributes of Coil Winding Department (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Background (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Industrial Lighting of the National Research Council and Hawthorne (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Culture of Hawthorne (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Discovering Hawthorne's "Roots" (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hawthorne: Getting the Story Straight (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - The Hawthorne Studies, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript for "New Light on Hawthorne" (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Peg Count (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Snow's Final Conclusions (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Where the Devil Works (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Why the Hawthorne Myth Dies Hard (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Pages 2-180 Not Complete (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Pages 181-435 Not Complete (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Pages 436-661 Not Complete (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Henry Landsberger "Hawthorne Revisited", 1958 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - The Hawthorne Experiment's First Statistical Interpretation, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Lighting the Way: First Quantitative Analysis of the Hawthorne Illumination Experiment of 1924-1927, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Mayo at the Hawthorne Works 1928-1932, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Review of Academy of Met Review article 87-205 "The Sudden Restlessness of Relay Assembly Operator 2A", 1987 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hawthorne Papers By Richard Franke, 1987-1991 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Harvard Business School Website 2007 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Steve Levitt & John List on "Hawthorne Effect", 2009 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Bramel and Friend Pages on Hawthorne (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Hawthorne Museum (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Symposium - "Hawthorne: Getting the Story Straight" (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Sheets for Review of Hawthorn Myth Article (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - "A Square Deal for His Wife", 1917 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - The Talking Movies, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Dubois Paper at AT&T (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Mention of Feb. 13, 1924 Dinner
  - Non-Theatrical Films NY Times April 5, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    p. 22:4
  - WE News "The Movies of Industry" April 1928 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Volume 17 #2, pp. 10-11
  - Recording the Sound Pictures, 1929-1930 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - WE News - "Industrial Talking Pictures" February 1932, pp. 14, 15, 44 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Lovette & Watkins on 20 years of talking pictures, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Edward M. Kellogg, History of Sound Motion Picture SMPTE 1955 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    June, pp. 291-308; July, 356-374; August, 422- 437